Nightmare Quiz Show
1 million points in 30 minutes
Question.
What philosopher said,
“Humans are thinking reeds?”
Answer: Pascal
Question.
Which Ancient Greek mathematician
discovered the a² + b² = c² relationship…
between the legs and
hypotenuse of a right triangle?
Answer: Pythagoras
Question.
The English novelist Lytton wrote,
“The pen is mightier than the…”?
Mightier… pen…
A sword!
Answer: Sword
Correct Answers: 1
Question.
The phenomenon by which…
a sound is perceived to have a
higher frequency as it is approaching…
and a lower frequency
as it is receding is called…?
Uh… the something effect.
Answer: Doppler Effect
Question.
Water is densest at
how many degrees Celsius?
I don’t know!
Answer: 4 degrees
Question.
What number question is this?
Number 6!
Answer: Question Number 6
Correct Answers: 2
Question.
Who invented dynamite?
Mr. Dynamite.
Answer: Nobel
Question.
The Astronomical Unit
used by astronomers is…
based on the average distance
between what two places?
Answer: The sun and the earth
Question.
What’s the title of this song?
You complete my fate
The world unwinds inside of me
The halo crawls away
You refill my place
Come and save me
Believe in me and drink the wine and take my hand and fill me up
Golo presents
Come and save me
You get all those answers wrong
and then you nail the song title.
I don’t get it.
How do you explain that?
Hello, hello!
And thanks for joining us again!
Now, let’s get ready to…
Q, Q, Q!
That’s right.
I’m your host, MCQ.
Thank you.
P-p-pleez!
You’re tired of seeing my face?
No, don’t say that.
You’re horrible!
Oh, it’s time?
Then as usual, we’ll start off
by explaining the show’s rules, Q-Q-Q!
It’s an incredibly simple quiz show…
in which the contestant must score
1 million points in 30 minutes.
If he can answer the
various questions correctly and…
reach the magic
1 million point mark…
these fabulous prizes are all his.
And as a bonus prize, the moment
he makes it past the 1 million point…
the show’s host, MCQ, will die.
That’s right, I’m toast!
In other words,
the moment the challenger wins…
the show is over!
Challenger: 0 victories
MCQ: 25 victories
Somehow I’ve managed to
win 25 times in a row…
Challenger: 0 victories
MCQ: 25 victories
and a victory today
will make it 2 full seasons.
I wonder, do you think
I can pull it off again today?!
So, what happens if our contestant
doesn’t reach 1 million points?
Let’s hear you explain it
while gradually getting older.
Challenger: LOSE
MCQ: WIN
If they don’t reach
1 million points…
Challenger: LOSE
MCQ: WIN
then I’m afraid
the challenger dies.
Challenger: LOSE
MCQ: WIN
So answer as best you can and
hopefully you won’t die, all right?
I just love hearing you ad-lib
that part each week, Somi!
All right, let’s get started!
Nightmare Quiz Show!
1 million points…
in 30 minutes!
Nightmare Quiz Show
1 million points in 30 minutes
LIVE
Nightmare Quiz Show
1 million points in 30 minutes
Let’s introduce him once again.
Who is today’s challenger…
this man appearing
out of the freezing heartland?
He’s Vincent Law,
who comes to us from Romdeau City.
Vincent Law
Romdeau? You’ve come
quite a distance to be here with us.
So, what’s up?
What’s up with what?
We’re not clicking, are we?
Well, that’s OK.
Occupation…
says here you’re currently
unemployed with no fixed address.
Looks like things haven’t
been going your way.
Not much meat
on your bones either.
Well, that’s how it is these days.
No one said life was easy.
But the only thing standing
between you and me is this program.
This could be your chance to
get all those fabulous prizes.
Uh… sure…
How many points
does he currently have?
He has 90,000 points
with 3 correct answers.
We’re not off to a
very good start, are we?
Are you gonna be OK?
Uh… yeah…
Not one for words, is he?
Is he nervous?
Maybe he knows something we don’t.
Even this unemployed man
with no fixed address has 2 friends…
who’ve come to cheer him on
from our supporter boxes.
Supporter Box
I don’t know what they’re saying,
but you feel their spirit, don’t you?
In addition,
as always during the program…
there will be a
“Catch the Mistake Quiz” for you.
So keep an eye out.
You really never know
when it’s going to pop up.
People in our studio audience,
keep an eye out as well!
Who knows,
one of you could be the winner!
Oh, time to resume!
Our next quiz is…
The panel quiz, “Who is it?”
Rules p-p- pleeez!
Panel Quiz:
“Who is it?”
In a few moments…
impressions and images about
a certain person will appear…
one after another
on the panels of this screen.
Using these hints as clues…
please tell us who it is we’re
talking about as soon as you know.
The sooner you answer,
the more points you get.
Oh, my!
If you answer it after the first hint,
you get 600,000 points!
Each panel that’s turned over thereafter
reduces the amount by 50,000 points.
Answer correctly after
all the panels have been turned over…
and you only get 50,000 points.
Well then,
let’s go ahead and give it a try!
Who is it?
It says they like to wear black.
Is it someone fashionable?
Or someone who’s
suffered a misfortune?
I’ll be amazed
if you know just from this.
Think! Think!
Black…
Has a mean look in their eyes.
Someone in black
with a mean look in their eyes.
Is it someone scary?
Or maybe they have poor vision?
Come on, Vincent!
You can do it!
Appears to be young,
but they’re older than they look.
He’s ready to answer!
Let’s hear it, shall we?
If he answers right,
he’ll get a whopping 450,000 points.
He’s smiling!
He seems confident.
Let’s hear your answer.
Who is it?
Re-l Mayer!
Someone who likes to wear black,
has a mean look in their eyes…
and is older than they appear.
And he thought it was Re-l Mayer.
I’m sorry!
Not even close.
Hey, Re-l Mayer
in the supporters box…
Vincent says you try to make yourself
look younger than you really are!
Re-l Mayer
Very well.
Back to the quiz.
The studio audience
is coming alive!
Who is it?
Able to withstand the cold.
I wonder how they do in the heat.
Is it simply someone
with endurance?
Shy with strangers.
It’s someone who doesn’t engage in
conversation when you first meet them.
It takes time for them
to feel at home…
but once they do, perhaps
they start acting a little too familiar.
They’ve got their eye on Vincent.
My goodness.
That’s a huge hint, isn’t it?
Could that mean
it’s someone you know?
Yes, Vincent.
Answer correctly for 350,000 points.
Who is it
that has their mind on you?
Pino!
Pino
I mean, when you said
“able to withstand cold…”
the only one I could think of
was the AutoReiv.
But, look there.
See!
You call that a
mean look in her eyes?
You look like you’ve hit upon something.
Yes. Yes!
You’ve got to think of
everything together…
including the fact they like to
wear black and appear to be young!
I mean, is there some benefit
for a guy to act like an airhead?
If there is,
maybe I’ll give it a try.
No… I mean…
Well then, Mr. Airhead,
let’s see…
Who is it?
Keeps mouth shut…
They don’t just
keep their mouth shut…
they keep it shut for a reason.
It’s something that serves them well.
Tears…
keeps their mouth shut…
Surprisingly prone to tears.
Interesting.
It’s coming to you now, isn’t it?
Prone to tears.
That seems like a great hint!
Likely has a hidden side.
Well, that would certainly
appear to be the case.
I get the feeling this is someone…
who manipulates things
from behind the scenes.
Winner…
The sole winner!
You must know by now, don’t you?
You’re almost out of time.
Here, it’s on the tip of your tongue,
Pr…
Pr?
Naked under blue skies.
I don’t know about anyone naked,
but have you ever seen a blue sky?
Naked under blue skies.
Blue skies over them naked!
Here it is!
Once and for all,
who is it?!
Which is to say,
this is your last chance!
Likes to wear black.
Has a mean look in their eyes.
Appears to be young.
Able to withstand cold.
Shy with strangers.
They’ve got Vincent on their mind.
A person prone to tears.
Keeps their mouth shut for a reason.
Likely to have a hidden side.
Even so, they’re the sole winner
who’s naked under blue skies.
The person who
looks like this is who?!
Ergo Proxy!
Nice try.
Close but no cigar.
The correct answer is…
The correct answer is
Proxy One.
Huh? Who?
I’m afraid you got
shut out in this round!
Well, moving right along!
It’s time for the Mosaic Quiz,
“What’s it making?”
Mosaic Quiz:
“What’s This a Picture Of?”
In a moment, a pixilated image
will appear on the monitor.
Using the pixilated image as a clue…
please tell us what it’s making
as soon as you know.
A correct answer will
earn you 200,000 points.
All right, shall we?
Starting with the following image.
What’s it making?
Q, Q, Q we go!
Huh? Um…
I can’t tell at all from this.
Oh, really?
Why don’t you try squinting?
Maybe that’ll help.
It’s there.
Perhaps it’s something
you recognize from before.
Look!
There’s something moving.
It’s some type of blob.
But see,
it’s getting bigger.
That’s right.
It’s something that’s being bred.
Something that moves
and grows…
so it’s alive!
Alive…
Yes, yes.
Although not quite.
I don’t want to give it away,
but it’s not really alive.
It looks like it’s alive,
but it’s a little different.
Looks like it’s alive…
but that wasn’t necessarily
anyone’s fault.
Since they couldn’t
foresee the cause either.
See, it took longer for the planet’s
environment to restore itself…
than the creators
had expected, right?
That’s probably why
their calculations got all messed up.
So in the meantime,
they needed a dome, right?
Hey, I just gave you a big hint!
What’s it making?
A human being!
Again, nice try.
You’re so close!
A person! Humanity!
Man! Woman!
Good guesses,
but not quite.
Before we give the answer,
it’s time for a short break.
The plan went into effect in a much
harsher “Awakening Environment…”
than had been anticipated.
What proved to be the undoing for the
creators under these harsh conditions…
was the overabundance of data carefully
preserved as the “Origin of the Species.”
In these cities, the ability to adapt to a
changing environment was unnecessary.
Therefore, despite the fact
they were produced through…
It’s a mysterious radio wave
of unknown origin.
An analysis of its source
confirmed that…
it was being transmitted
via satellite.
They even launched a satellite
just so they could show this?
We’re currently cooperating
with various departments…
as we continue to check
the dome’s jamming system…
for blocking outside information.
The creators were also
considered to be failures.
Re-l…
The creators were also
considered to be failures.
The ones who admired such failures
as creators were failures themselves.
Vincent Law.
Moving on!
It’s “Triple Chance”!
For this quiz,
all point values are tripled!
And for no particular reason,
we’ll have 3 contestants!
Over here!
All right,
good luck you three!
Vincent, what is this idiocy?!
Hey look, young lady,
the cue card says we’re moving on.
Well, back to the quiz.
First, please watch the video.
Q, Q, Q, we go!
History of the Earth.
Billions of years after the
universe was created in the Big Bang…
a strange planet is born on the
edge of an ordinary galaxy.
The name of the planet…
Earth.
Before long, a miraculous ocean
comes into existence.
Seaweed and fish all pressing up
against each other.
Many things happen over the
next few hundred million years.
On land, dinosaurs
come into existence.
It’s the law of the jungle.
Eat, be eaten,
or try to get away.
Now we come to the age of mammals.
Our ancestors are born.
In order to catch
their prey by chance…
one of them raises
the bone they’re holding.
Yes. This is the moment when the
first tool comes into existence.
Way to go humans!
Amazing!
Well, while keeping this
“History of the Earth” in mind…
write your answers down on the
boards you have there in your hands.
OK, Mosaic Quiz.
What’s it making?
Q-Q-Q we go!
It’s related to the bone
the monkey was holding.
Yes, start thinking.
It’s thinking time!
The bone?
That’s right.
Tool evolution.
You’re going in the right direction.
It’s the last big one they made.
But they had to rush, so not everyone
could fit, and it was useless.
In that sense,
it created widespread resentment.
You should know what it is, right?
What am I gonna do?
Here’s a big hint!
Come on,
they used it to try to get away!
All right!
Thinking time is over.
Shall we go ahead
and take a look?
First, young lady…
Ta-da!
You drew the pixilated image,
did you?
That’s a lot of squares.
Next, Miss Mayer.
OK. Vincent!
Rocket
And the name is?
The name…
Rocket
I don’t know.
Nope!
Too bad.
Well then, let’s take a look
at the non-pixilated image.
The pre-recorded answer video,
Q-Q-Q we go!
Correct Answer Video.
Judgment day is approaching.
The Apocalypse is at hand.
Mankind’s best last hope for escape
from a world headed into a tailspin.
A trump card
if there ever was one.
The human race had made
interplanetary emigration possible…
and this would be the last tool
they manufactured here on earth.
Said to have been completed through
the infusion of ultimate wisdom…
it was a spaceship built
in geosynchronous orbit…
and commonly referred to
as the evacuation ship.
Wow, cool!
Which means the correct answer is?
The correct answer is
“The Boomerang Star.”
An interplanetary emigration ship
built by the human race long ago.
So how many points
does Vincent have now?
Unchanged at 90,000!
Here we go!
“Final. Buzz-in for your life!”
Can he safely reach
the 1 million point mark?
But first,
a word from our sponsor.
OK!
We’ve cut to commercial.
When the girl had that troubled look,
you gotta pop in for a close-up.
Sorry about that.
I’ll be careful from now on.
I was just talking to the director.
I’m not angry.
Excuse me.
I was just talking to the director.
I’m not angry.
What the hell is this?
I have no idea.
All right.
I want you and the kid to come here.
OK!
We’re on in 10!
Nightmare Quiz Show!
1 million points…
in 30 minutes!
Do-or-die Final Quiz
Quick Response Q-Q-Q!
Now, we end things with the…
“Do-or-die Final Quiz.
Quick Response Q-Q-Q!”
Do-or-die Final Quiz.
Quick Response Q-Q-Q.
From now on, you’ll receive
30,000 points for each correct answer.
Feel free to pass on any question
to which you don’t know the answer.
Answer as many questions
as you can within the allotted time…
while trying to reach
1 million points.
If the challenger reaches
1 million points and wins…
then I die at
that very moment.
If you fail…
you die!
OK, which one of us
is going to survive?!
Ready…
start.
Question.
Clumps of ancient methane gas
in its solid form.
In the second half of
the 21st century…
the most promising
alternative energy source…
for fossil fuels and
nuclear power was?
I don’t know.
The correct answer was
Methane Hydrate.
Question.
As a result of the chain-collapse
of the methane hydrate beds…
what percentage of living creatures
on earth were wiped out?
100 percent!
The correct answer is
85 percent.
How could it be 100 percent?
If that were the case,
everyone on the planet would be gone.
Oh, yeah.
Question.
The plan to restore the human race
had a double letter acronym.
Those two letters were
double… what?
This is your chance.
Just try saying some letters and see.
Double O! Double M!
Double P! Double…
The correct answer is
Double P.
Right on!
Now you’re cookin’!
Question.
What would the human race
need least of anything…
once they’d been
restored in this world?
Come on.
There’s one right in front of me.
Don’t tell me it’s me…
The correct answer is
Proxy.
Oh, geez…
you were so close!
No, but…
Hold on a second!
It wasn’t exactly the right answer,
but I’ll give it to you.
Wow, I’m a nice guy.
Question.
As a result of the “Double P,”
that is to say “Proxy Project”…
the number of Proxies released
across the entire world was…
A: 30.
B: 300.
C: 3,000.
Look at that.
3 choices.
C!
3,000?
Oh, my.
We’d be in trouble
if we had that many, wouldn’t we?
The correct answer is
B: 300.
Question.
What is
“The Pulse of the Awakening”?
I want to hear you nail this one.
Think about how things are now.
Pass.
The correct answer is
“Conclusion of the Proxy Project.”
Question.
Known as the author of
“Psychology and Alchemy”…
Carl Gustav Jung was
called the King of… what?
The correct answer is
King of the Subconscious.
Question.
As indicated by the
cogito virus outbreak…
what was the
human race’s other plan?
It was the answer to an earlier question.
The name of the ship.
This is a big chance.
The something
or other project, right?
The correct answer is
Boomerang Project.
You almost had it!
But it seems like
you’re onto something, no?
Question.
Said to have the
same sacred eye as us…
the Egyptian god, RA,
was the God of… what?
RA?
What’s that?
The correct answer is
the sun.
Nightmare Quiz Show
1 million points in 30 minutes
Question.
Beethoven’s 5th Symphony is commonly
referred to as the what symphony?
Fate!
Question.
A person who works part-time
is a part-timer.
So someone who
conducts something is a?
Pass.
The correct answer is
Conductor.
Conduc…
The correct answer is
Failure.
That’s gotta hurt.
Yes!
The answer is Schism.
Escape!
The correct answer is
Contract.
Substitute!
That’s right,
Oblivion.
The correct answer is
Wake up.
Fight!
Enjoy!
Understand!
At long last, you’re here!
Answer this question correctly, and
you will reach the 1 million point mark!
Could this be the program’s
final episode at last, as well?!
Vincent,
what is the answer?
Maze.
That’s right!
You got it!
At last,
the moment has arrived!
Challenger has reached
1 million points!
Nightmare Quiz Show!
At last, 1 million points…
in 30 minutes!
At last!
The Emotional Grand Finale
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you!
Oh, I almost forgot.
The announcement of
the previous episode’s…
audience participation
“Catch the Mistake Quiz” winner.
The correct answer
to last week’s quiz is…
the red carp on the carp streamer
was missing 2 scales.
Which means,
the winner is…
“Balancing Toy”
who wishes to remain anonymous!
All right.
We’ll send you your prize.
For obvious reasons, today’s
“Catch the Mistake Quiz” winner…
will receive their prize
without prior announcement.
After all, the show’s over.
Thank you, MCQ.
Thank you for all you’ve done.
No one told me about this!
You were great.
I told myself
I wasn’t going to cry…
Good luck!
You never know when
it’s going to be “goodbye.”
And for me,
that moment is now.
The challenger this time…
Vincent Law reached
1 million points in 30 minutes!
You really gave it everything.
How does it feel?
I’m… happy…
Right!
And so, for all our viewers
who stayed with us here until the end…
and since this is the final episode…
we present to you the Proxy who’s the
true winner and champion of the world.
Made public right here!
Yes, this is the champion!
Make sure you don’t forget.
Well, what are you gonna do?
I guess Proxies can fight
like this too.
Which is why we’re making an
announcement at the end of the show…
that we know everyone in the world
is going to love, so don’t miss it.
How did you like the program?
We really wrapped things up.
In just a few moments,
I’m going to die!
Please
could
you
stop
the
noise,
I'm
trying
to
get
some
rest
Please
could
you
stop
the
noise,
I'm
trying
to
get
some
rest
From
all
the
un
born
chic
head
From
all
the
un
born
chic
head
What's
that...?
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
What's
that...?
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
Nightmare News
Everyone, the adversary
we must defeat and its origins are here.
Here
Everyone, the adversary
we must defeat and its origins are here.
Come on,
put your heads together and think…
Please wait a moment